const questions: Array<QuestionType> = [
  {
    question: 'אָכַל',
    answers: ['hij at'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'גָּנַב',
    answers: ['hij stal', 'hij misleidde'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'דְּמוּת',
    answers: ['gelijkenis'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'דַּעַת',
    answers: ['kennis', 'verstand', 'benul', 'begrip'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הַיּוֹם',
    answers: ['vandaag', 'heden'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'הֵיכָל',
    answers: ['heiligdom', 'tempel', 'paleis'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חֹדֶשׁ',
    answers: ['maand', 'nieuwe maan'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'חוֹמָה',
    answers: ['muur'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'כָּתַב',
    answers: ['hij schreef'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'לָכֵן',
    answers: ['daarom', 'zodoende', 'derhalve'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'מַלְכּוּת',
    answers: ['koningschap', 'koninkrijk'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נֶגֶב',
    answers: ['zuiden', 'Negev', 'woestijn', 'droge streek', 'zuid'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'נָתַן',
    answers: ['hij gaf', 'hij zette'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עָמַד',
    answers: ['hij stond'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'עָשָׂה',
    answers: ['hij deed', 'hij maakte'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'צֹאן',
    answers: ['kleinvee', 'kudde', 'schapen', 'geiten'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'צַדִּיק',
    answers: ['rechtvaardig', 'rechtvaardige', 'vroom', 'vrome', 'godvrezend', 'godvrezende'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  },
  {
    question: 'צֶלֶם',
    answers: ['beeld', 'gelijkenis', 'afbeelding', 'tekening'],
    type: 'woordenschat'
  }
]
const lesson12Vocabulary: LessonType = {
  id: 'lesson12-vocabulary',
  name: 'Les 12 – Woordenschat',
  type: 'woordenschat',
  active: false,
  questions
}
export default lesson12Vocabulary
